

Hi I am,

Yvonne

About me

Experienced in web develoment, programming, and design, alongside other diverse skills. Able to self manage during independent work and collaborative in team settings. Passionate about learning new things. Ready to contribute with enthusiasm and a strong work ethic.

Interest

Enthusiastic explorer of new games and a experimental culinary hobbyist . I also find inspiration in documentaries and web video/novel series which can offer new perspectives and allow me to delve deep into the subjects/ topics of interest.

Contact Me

Yvonne Yen



evon.work2@gmail.com
yvonyen8
https://tinyurl.com/yuesnmme

Career Objectives

Seeking a challenging and fulfilling career that can ultilize my personal growth to make a positive impact through learning and pushing for mutual success.

Key Skills

- Office software
 Design
 Web development
 Programming & Database
- Communication
 Life long learning
 Problem solving
 Teamwork

Work Experiences

F&B

>Service Crew & Manager (Part-Time) Kiwami Ramen & Gyoza Bar | Sep 2021 - Jan 2023

>Service Crew Aburi En | Feb 2021 - Sep 2021

- Build good rapport and addressing customer's queries and feedback.
- Guide staff on shift procedures and in reccomendation of menu items
- Preparation of desserts and alcoholic and non alcoholic drinks.
- Monitor guest wait list, and allocate seats for guest(w/reservation)
- Conduct daily reconciliation of sales

>Digital Ambassador IMDA | Jun 2020 - Jan 2021 **Information Tech**

- Encourage the onboarding of e-payment for hawkers
- Taught seniors and address seniors queries both online and offline
- Assist with administrative work: post event mails & data entry

Education

>Republic Polytechnic [Apr 2022 - Current] Diploma in Digital Design and Development

>Institute of Technical Education [2012 -2013] Nitec in Interactive Media Design